Preliminary Guide to the H. Keith H. Brodie, President, Records, 1963 - 1994 UA.03.61.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Subject Files, 1963-1994, bulk 1985-1993
  - Subject Files, 1964-1993 and undated, bulk 1985-1993. Accession A2004-28.
    - Board of Trustees Files, 1985-1993.
      - Trustees: Minnick, Carlton, 1989 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 113)
      - Trustees: Muller, William H. Jr., 1985 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 113)
      - Trustees: Nahmias, David, 1985 July 1-1986 June 30 (Box 114)
      - Trustees: Nelson, Margaret M., 1989 Feb. 1-1989 July 31 (Box 114)
      - Trustees: Nicholas, Peter, 1992 Oct. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 114)
      - Trustees: November, Martin T., 1986 Feb. 1-1987 July 31 (Box 114)
      - Trustees: Parrish, Alexander W., 1987 Mar. 1-1987 June 30 (Box 114)
      - Trustees: Patterson, Eugene, 1988 May 1-1993 June 30 (Box 114)
      - Trustees: Postma, Herman, 1986 Dec. 1-1992 June 30 (Box 114)
      - Trustees: Pratt, Edmund T., 1985 July 1-1991 Dec. 31 (Box 114)
      - Trustees: Reid, Elizabeth Brooks, 1986 Apr. 1-1992 June 30 (Box 114)
      - Trustees: Reuben-Cooke, Wilhelmina M., 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 114)
      - Trustees: Robinson, George, 1993 Mar. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 114)
      - Trustees: Rowlett, Margaret F., 1990 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 114)
      - Trustees: Schaefer, Norb, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 114)
      - Trustees: Sears, Amy E., 1988 Feb. 1-1989 Dec. 31 (Box 114)
      - Trustees: Semans, Truman, 1993 Mar. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 114)
      - Trustees: Sidman, Edwin, 1989 Feb. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 114)
      - Trustees: Simpson, Dorothy, 1987 June 1-1993 June 30 (Box 114)
      - Trustees: Spaulding, Jean, 1993 Mar. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 114)
      - Trustees: Stern, Kay Goodman, 1986 July 1-1989 Aug. 31 (Box 114)
      - Trustees: Stockton, Thomas B., 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 114)
      - Trustees: Temple, Arthur, 1985 July 1-1986 Dec. 31 (Box 114)
      - Trustees: Thomas, R. David, 1988 Feb. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 114)
      - Trustees: Tobias, Randall, 1986 Oct. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 114)
      - Trustees: Tosteson, Daniel, 1987 Mar. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 114)
      - Trustees: Wester, Thaddeus, 1986 July 1-1991 July 31 (Box 114)
      - Trustees: Williams, A. Morris, 1988 Sept. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 114)
      - Trustees: Williams, L. Neil Jr., 1987 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 114)
      - Trustees: Wilson, Gary, 1992 Oct. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 114)
      - Trustees: Woodruff, Judy, 1985 June 1-1993 June 30 (Box 114)
      - Trustees: Yoh, Harold, 1991 June 1-1993 June 30 (Box 114)
      - Trustees: Younger, Kenneth G. Jr., 1985 June 1-1991 June 30 (Box 114)
      - Trustee-Dinners, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 114)
      - Trustees-Emeriti, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 114)
      - Trustee-Executive Committee, 1985 July 1-1987 Dec. 31 (Box 114)
      - Trustee Mailings, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 114)
      - Trustee Manual, 1988 Aug. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 114)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: Cities, Miscellaneous, 1985 July 1-1987 June 30 (Box 114)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: Atlanta, 1986 Apr. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 114)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: Baltimore, 1986 Sept. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 114)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: Boston, 1987 Mar. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 114)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: California, 1988 Mar. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 114)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: Charlotte, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 114)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: Chicago, 1985 June 1-1993 June 30 (Box 114)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: Cleveland, 1989 Aug. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 114)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: Columbia, SC, 1990 Apr. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 115)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: Connecticut, 1986 Jan. 1 1-1993 June 30 (Box 115)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: Dallas, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 115)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: Delaware, 1988 Apr. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 115)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: Detroit, 1989 June 1-1993 June 30 (Box 115)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: Florida, 1989 Apr. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 115)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: Miami, 1986 Dec. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 115)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: New Jersey, 1989 May 1-1993 June 30 (Box 115)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: New Orleans, LA, 1991 May 1-1993 June 30 (Box 115)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: Greensboro, 1990 Nov. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 115)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: New York, 1987 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 115)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: Philadelphia, 1986 Jan. 1 1-1993 June 30 (Box 115)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: Pinehurst, 1989 Apr. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 115)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: Raleigh, 1987 Jan. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 115)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: Richmond, 1987 Aug. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 115)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: St. Louis, 1988 June 1-1993 June 30 (Box 115)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: Washington, D.C., 1987 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 115)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: Winston-Salem, 1988 Mar. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 115)
    - Faculty Arts And Sciences Campaign, 1985 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 115)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: Joel Fleishman, 1990 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 115)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign: Miscellaneous, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 115)
    - Arts & Sciences Campaign For Duke, 1989 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 115)
    - Campaign For Duke: Executive Committee, 1988 Feb. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 115)
    - Arts & Sciences, Steering Committee, 1987 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 115)
    - Capital Campaign Executive Committee, 1987 Apr. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 115)
  - Subject Files, 1977-1994, bulk 1985-1993. Accession UA2001-10.
    - Aquaculture Task Force, 1988 Mar.-1988 Apr. (Box 116)
    - Athletic Council, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 116)
    - Athletic Council, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 116)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Conflict of Interest, 1990 Feb. 1-1992 June 30 (Box 116)
    - Bicycling Task Force, 1990 Nov. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 116)
    - Black Undergraduate Student 30th Year Anniversary Celebration Comm., 1992 Mar. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 116)
    - Cleland Endowment Fund Committee, 1985 May 1-1987 Apr. 30 (Box 116)
    - Discrimination Committee, Biracial), 1988 Nov. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 116)
    - Discrimination in the Classroom, Committee on, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 116)
    - East Campus Enhancement Committee, 1990 May 1-1993 June 30 (Box 116)
    - Facilities and Environment, Committee on, 1992 July 2-1993 June 30 (Box 116)
    - Facilities and Environment, Committee on, 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 116)
    - Facilities and Environment, Committee on, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 116)
    - Faculty Governance Task Force Committee, 1989 July 1-1989 July 31 (Box 116)
    - Faculty Voting Privileges Committee, 1986 Oct. 1-1987 Nov. 30 (Box 116)
    - Family and Child Care Issues, Committee for, 1990 Oct. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 116)
    - Founders' Day Planning Committee, 1986 Apr. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 116)
    - Founders' Day Planning Committee, 1985 Nov. 1-1986 Apr. 30 (Box 116)
    - Gift Policy Committee, University, 1990 Oct. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 116)
    - Healthcare Oversight Committee, 1989 July 1-1991 Oct. 30 (Box 116)
    - Information Systems Committee, 1990 June 1-1993 June 30 (Box 117)
    - Judicial Board, University, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 117)
    - Licensing of University Indicia Committee, 1982 Oct. 1-1991 Mar. 30 (Box 117)
    - Minority Affairs Review Committee, 1987 Mar. 11-1990 June 30 (Box 117)
    - National Association of Black Students for Educational Advancement (NABSEA), 1989 July 1-1991 May 31 (Box 117)
    - Nondiscrimination Committee, University, 1991 Mar. 1-1993 June 30 (Box 117)
    - Parking Task Force, 1988 Nov. 1-1992 Oct. 31 (Box 117)
    - Patent Committee, 1983 July 1-1993 Mar. 31 (Box 117)
    - Policy Implementation Committee, 1986 May 1-1987 May 31 (Box 117)
    - President's Committee on the Recruitment & Retention of Black Faculty, 1988 Apr. 1-1988 May 31 (Box 117)
    - President's Council on Black Affairs, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 117)
    - President's Council on Black Affairs, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 117)
    - President's Council on Black Affairs Subcommittee, 1992 May 1-1992 July 31 (Box 117)
    - Recreational Facilities Committee, 1992 Jan. 1-1993 Apr. 30 (Box 117)
    - Research Policy Committee, 1990 Jan. 1-1991 Sept. 30 (Box 117)
    - Smith, Eleanor, 1988 Sept. 1-1990 Mar. 31 (Box 117)
    - Social Implications of Duke's Investments Committee, 1986 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 117)
    - Social Implications of Duke's Investments Committee, 1986 Mar. 1-1986 June 30 (Box 118)
    - Social Implications of Duke's Investments Committee, 1985 Nov. 1-1986 Feb. 28 (Box 118)
    - Social Implications of Duke's Investments Committee, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 118)
    - Staff Fringe Benefits, Standing Committee on, 1972 Mar. 1-1992 Feb. 28 (Box 118)
    - Undergraduate Enrollment Committee, 1989 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 118)
    - University Judicial Board Committee, 1976 Nov. 1-1991 June 30 (Box 118)
    - University Union Board, 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 118)
    - University Union Board, 1971 Oct. 1-1991 June 30 (Box 118)
    - Duke-Africa Initiative, 1985 Dec. 1-1986 Apr. 30 (Box 118)
    - Faculty, Black, 1986 Oct. 1-1989 June 30 (Box 118)
    - MCNC, 1984 Nov. 1-1991 June 30 (Box 118)
    - Research Triangle Foundation, 1992 Apr. 1-1992 June 30 (Box 118)
    - Research Triangle Foundation, 1991 July 1-1992 Mar. 31 (Box 118)
    - Research Triangle Foundation, 1990 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 119)
    - Research Triangle Foundation, 1989 July 1-1990 June 30 (Box 119)
    - Research Triangle Foundation, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 119)
    - Research Triangle Foundation, 1985 July 1-1987 June 30 (Box 119)
    - Research Triangle Foundation BOD Meeting, 1989 Aug. 1-1990 Jan. 31 (Box 119)
    - Research Triangle Institute, 1992 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 119)
    - Research Triangle Institute, 1991 July 1-1992 June 30 (Box 119)
    - Research Triangle Institute, 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 119)
    - Research Triangle Institute, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 120)
    - Research Triangle Institute, 1985 July 1-1987 June 30 (Box 120)
    - Shanties, 1986 Apr. 1-1986 Apr. 4 (Box 120)
    - South Africa: Divestment, 1986 July 1-1987 Apr. 30 (Box 120)
    - South Africa: Divestment, 1986 May 1-1986 June 30 (Box 120)
    - South Africa: Divestment, 1986 Jan. 1-1986 Apr. 30 (Box 120)
    - South Africa: Divestment, 1985 Sept. 1-1985 Dec. 31 (Box 120)
    - South Africa: Divestment, 1985 Jan. 1-1985 Aug. 30 (Box 120)
    - South Africa: Divestment, 1983 Apr. 1-1984 Dec. 31 (Box 120)
    - South Africa: Divestment Responses, 1986 May 1-1987 Mar. 30 (Box 120)
    - South Africa, 1986 Jan. 1-1987 Apr. 30 (Box 120)
    - South Africa, 1985 Mar. 1-1985 Dec. 31 (Box 121)
    - South Africa: Petition, 1985 Jan. 23 (Box 121)
    - South Africa: Replies to ASDU Letter, 1985 Sept. 1-1985 Nov. 30 (Box 121)
    - South African Scholarships, 1986 May 1-1987 Apr. 30 (Box 121)
    - Southern Association of Colleges & Schools (SACS), 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 121)
    - SACS, 1987 July 1-1989 June 30 (Box 121)
    - SACS, 1986 May 1-1987 June 30 (Box 121)
    - SACS Accreditation Visit, 1987 June 1-1989 Apr. 30 (Box 121)
    - Triangle Universities Center for Advanced Studies, Inc., 1991 July 1-1993 June 30 (Box 121)
    - Triangle Universities Center for Advanced Studies, Inc., 1989 July 1-1991 June 30 (Box 121)
    - Triangle Universities Center for Advanced Studies, Inc., 1977 Sept. 1-1989 June 30 (Box 121)
    - Triangle Universities Center for Advanced Studies, Inc., 1985 June 1-1987 June 30 (Box 121)
    - Executive Compensation Surveys, 1985, 1987 (Box 121)